ARYAN MOUSAVI

PROFILE

I am a versatile software developer who was born in 1998, with over a decade of personal experience in the field. And around 5 years of professional job experience. My expertise spans across multiple programming languages, including **C#**, **C++**, **Python**, and **Dart** (with Flutter framework). I have a strong foundation in the mathematics of **AI** (ML and DL) and have built my own Deep Learning AI framework from scratch to gain a deeper understanding of this fascinating field. I also have experience building projects in **Unreal** and **Unity** game engines.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER @ SHARIF UNIVERSITY - 2018-PRESENT

While I am bound by a Non-Disclosure Agreement that prevents me from sharing specific details, I can share that my experience includes completing various internal and commercial software products using **C#**, **C++**, **Dart**, **Python**, **Unreal Engine**, and **Pytorch** for a company by the name of <u>Pasargad Flight Pioneers</u>.

ENGLISH TEACHER @ MOTARJEMAN INSTITUTE - 2017-2018

Prior to my role as a software programmer, I worked as an English Teacher for almost a year.

FREELANCE PROGRAMMER AND COACH - 2016-PRESENT

- During my time as a programmer I've completed various projects and tasks mainly for individuals or as stand-alone products that I've sold. I've created a course for **C#** (albeit in Persian language) that covers everything from the very basics to the advanced topics of reflection and post-compilation code obfuscation. I have also created English courses on **C++** and **Unreal Engine C++** that are available in my YouTube channel.
- In addition to the courses, I have also created various security-related tools such as a watch-tower for managed and automatic bug bounty hunting (Not a bounty hunter myself, made it for a client).
- As a personal project, I made an Al-based virtual try-on on my own (arch based) home server alongside a mobile app that I wrote with flutter, the aim was that you could take a photo of any piece of clothing you saw through the shopping mall and the app would put it on your body so that you could try a piece of clothing without actually putting it on.
- I teach Python programming in a school located in Sistan and Baluchestan province as charity work.

EDUCATION

AZAD UNIVERSITY: COMPUTER SCIENCE BACHELOR

TEHRAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY – PYTHON | C++ | SEO | ML | CEH | JAVA

SKILLS AND SPECIALTIES

- Software Development / CI-CD / Git
- Fundamentals of Deep Learning, Custom / Non-Standard Deep Learning
- Unreal Engine C++ Programming
- Programming: C++, Python, C#, Dart
- Tools: Pytorch, Flutter, Linux, ...